loyolacollege.edu 2015-04-25

# Loyola College

                         Loyola College        (Autonomous),
                                 Chennai – 600 034.
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Loyola College website and reviewing our privacy policy.
We respect the privacy of those who visit our college web site. In accordance with
this, we have created this policy in order to demonstrate our privacy commitment to
our users
We collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that
information to us. We do not give, share, sell, or transfer any personal information to
a third party. If you want to know more about how we record non-personal
information about your visit or how we use information that you voluntarily submit,
read on
Non-personal Information We Record
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or
download information, our website's operating system will automatically record
some general information about your visit.
During your visit, our web operating system will record:
        The type of Operating System that you use (such as Windows, Unix, or Mac).
        The type of Browser (such as "Netscape version X" or "Internet Explorer version X")
        that you are using.
        The Date and Time you visit our site, and the web pages that you visit on our site.
        The Internet Domain for your Internet service, such as "xyz.com" or "xyz.net" if you
        use a private Internet access account or "yourcollege.edu" if you connect from a
        college or university domain.
We use this information for statistical analysis, to help us make our site more useful
to visitors. This tracking system does not record information about individuals.
